<?xml version="1.0"?>

<PropertyList>
        	<title>Lockheed Martin F-22A Raptor  V0.89</title>
			
			<key>
				<name>c</name>
				<desc>Toggle canopy</desc>
			</key>
						<key>
				<name>Joystick: Military Trigger</name>
				<desc>Fire Guns in missile mode</desc>
			</key>
			
			
			<key>
				<name>w</name>
				<desc>Switch the weapon type between guns and missiles</desc>
			</key>

			<key>
				<name>e</name>
				<desc>Fire the current weapon type</desc>
			</key>
			
			<key>
				<name>Ctrl+d</name>
				<desc>Toggle Center bay doors</desc>
			</key>
			<key>
				<name>Ctrl+F</name>
				<desc>Toggle Aim-9 bay doors</desc>
			</key>			
			<key>
				<name>l  (Lower-case L)</name>
				<desc>Launch flares</desc>
			</key>
			<key>
				<name>Shift-R</name>
				<desc>Toggle HUD Radar Silent/Active</desc>
			</key>
       		<key>
				<name>Shift-T</name>
				<desc>Toggle the FBW Override switch (0 is off 1 is on)</desc>
			</key>
			<key>
        			<name>q</name>
        			<desc>Reset to default view direction (works on all but pilot cam)</desc>
    			</key>
      <key>
        <name>r</name>
        <desc>Change Radar Distances</desc>
      </key>
      <key>
        <name>Shift-i</name>
        <desc>Toggle Experimental Dogfight Mode (Just for fun. Not actually usefull. yet...)</desc>
      </key>
      <key>
        <name>m</name>
        <desc>Select an Air to Air Weapon</desc>
      </key>
      <key>
        <name>n</name>
        <desc>Select an Air to ground Weapon</desc>
      </key>
      <key>
        <name>i</name>
        <desc>Select a DEBUG Missile</desc>
      </key>
	   <key>
        <name>y</name>
        <desc>Lock on to the Next Target</desc>
      </key>
	  
	  	   <key>
        <name>U</name>
        <desc>Toggle New Smoke winders </desc>
      </key>

			<!--Todo: Make a scroll bar.. some how...-->
			<line>Lockheed Martin F-22A</line>
			<line></line>
						<line></line>
			<line>---------------------------------Specifications:</line>

						<line>The debug XMAA Missile is a experimental 160nm Long range missile. Flys at mach 5</line>

			<line>Maximum speed: Mach 2.25 @ 65000ft: Mach 1.8+ @ sea level</line>
			<line>Super Cruise speed: Mach 1.10 20000-65000ft ~~ Mil Thrust</line>
			<line>Sustained turn rate (FBW ON): 28+ deg/sec </line>
			<line>Sustained turn rate (FBW OFF): 128+ deg/sec </line>
			<line>This plane can Super cruise</line>
			<line>Which means it can go faster than mach 1</line>
			<line>With no Afterburner</line>
			<line></line>
			<line>The radar hud is a special hud that will show you targets and which target your locked on too</line>
			<line></line>
<line>To turn on the Radar HUD, Press the switch on the lower right console that is labled power.</line>
<line>You will know its on when the green light just below the switch turns on, (You may have to press it twice when you spawn in)</line>
			<line></line>		
<line>To Start Raptor: Simply click the battery switch till its at main power (Twice) then Press the 2 JFS switches on the bottom left console. Then press the 2 cutoff switches.</line>
			<line>Next switch the 6 switches on the Electrical panel to turn on instruments, flight controls, Counter messures, and more. then click the POWER switch on the HUD panel to turn on the canvas hud</line>
<line>---------------------------------Some info on Flight dynamics and Fly by wire---------------------------------</line>
<line></line>
<line>Rotate around 185 With auto flaps</line>
<line>When the Gear is down, The Vectors will Lock up to the center position and stay in place to ease takeoffs and landings</line>
<line>The small left screen will show you flight data like aoa, and flaps setting (more coming soon)</line>
<line>The vectors go up +-30 degrees at max. The FBW will automaticly adjust the min and max according to your speed. You can disable the limiter with the FBW override switch</line>
<line>But it will only adjust it by +-10 degrees </line>
<line>You can turn OFF the vectors entirely with The vector shutoff switch. it is located on the lower right console</line>
<line></line>
<line>The FBW Will automaticly move the flaps into the most effective position when the gear is down. </line>
<line>Manuel control of the flaps is available when the gear is up</line>
<line>The FBW override switch disables the automatic flaps and allows you to control them no matter the gear possition</line>
<line></line>
			<line>RWR terminology: When you here 3 beeps: New Threat Deteced. When you here 1 beep: Redected threat.</line>
<line>When you here Repeated delayed beeps: a bandit is locked on you. When you hear repeated quick beeps Missile inbound! Missile will show on RWR</line>
<line>---------------------------------Autopilot:</line>

<line>The 3 buttons with right arrows disable the autopilot feature displayed in text to the right of the button Press Ctrl-c and youll see it</line>
<line>Text will light up on the front panel showing which feature is active</line>	
<line>Use the VS, ASI Up Down Rocker buttons to the right of the text panel to change the rates of the autopilot</line>	
<line>For heading: Wing leveler is only inplemented at the moment.</line>		
<line></line>
<line>We like to constantly add new cool things to Raptor! If you like this jet: Update it here! https://github.com/racerretrocoder/Flightgear-F-22A-Raptor</line>
<line>Me and snail hope you Love flying this jet! :D</line>

</PropertyList>
